Hi everyone. This is EYA. I want to
begin by welcoming you to my channel, to
this video.
This is the first
of a series of videos that we are doing
directed to church leaders.
Inclusive, of course, of pastors,
elders, deacons, Bible teachers, those
in Christian ministry across the earth.
And we have a message to bring to you.
We are seeing supernatural
Bible changes happen right now. Bible
prophecy is unfolding.
And before you stop this video, I
implore you,
please listen to what we have to say.
I've been walking with Jesus Christ for
more than three decades. I've never
fallen away.
I have
worn out several Bibles from reading
them and studying them. The changes that
we're seeing in the Bible now are so
obvious. In the beginning of June 2016,
I was made aware words like bank was in
the Bible.
Where that the lion had changed to the
wolf.
And I was heartsick.
And I said, "Lord, there must be other
brethren
who see these changes. I can't be the
only one. I can't be the only one who
sees."
And that's when the Lord laid it on my
heart to do a channel cuz I thought,
"If there's only one person I can find,
Lord, one person who can see these
blasphemous changes."
Are you the remnant?
Do you see the Bible changes?
Our hearts are grieved and troubled as
we have seen an attack on the Bible,
digital,
audio, paper Bibles.
Bibles that we've owned for years and
years are supernaturally changing.
And we beg of you
to please take the time to listen to
what we're going to share with you
right now and in subsequent videos in
this series.
I've been a Christian for for 43 years.
Um
and
in my mid-20s, I I
I you know, I read the the book The
Great Planet The Late Great Planet
Earth. And that really got me interested
in end-time prophecy.
So, I I've studied end-time prophecy
more than more than any other subject in
the Bible
um throughout the years and I spent a
lot of time on it.
And just been really aware of the things
things to look for.
And about 2 years ago, I found out that
there were certain changes to logos and
movies and things like that and I began
to investigate it.
And just a couple of days into
into studying this and trying to
determine what was going on, uh I found
out that the Bible was also changing.
And that was just I mean
an incredible shocker.
So, I started digging into this
and probably
2 weeks
or less after finding out, I went and I
spoke to my pastor.
And of course, you know, I was very
nervous about talking to him about this
and I was really unprepared and still
pretty much in shock.
And
basically after having that conversation
with him,
um he was very he was very measured. Uh
he didn't say whether he saw them or he
didn't see them,
but he did say that we have to be very
careful about how we proceed about this.
So, after that meeting, you know, I was
really kind of deflated because I
thought, you know, I would show him
these things and he would obviously see
it because of how well studied he is cuz
I've known the man for 30 years.
So, I was really taken back. So, at that
point, I decided, you know, I've got to
find some evidence. I've got to come up
with some type of evidence. I can't
just, you know, tell people that look at
these verses cuz obviously people aren't
remembering it the same way.
So, I probably spent about 6 to 8 months
doing a lot of digging,
um looking for evidence.
And um
that's really
um how my channel came about because I
realized that, you know, I felt like the
Lord put it on my heart to get this
information out here so people could
see, you know, some tangible evidence
of, you know, contradictions in the
Bible and
uh residual evidence that shows what
actually used to be in the Bible and
things like that. So,
um that's kind of been my passion and
the uh purpose of my channel.
And uh just really, you know,
hoping to get information out there to
to help wake up the church so they could
be aware of what's going on.
Yeah, I'm Jason and I've been born again
for about 32 years. And
I can say that the journey that I have
walked on has been one where
I've been very interested and very um
purposeful about living a biblical life
to the best of my
my ability. Uh I have I absolutely fell
in love with the word of God. Um never
had a moment's hesitation of of
believing and knowing um after coming
into relationship
with Jesus. And
it's been extremely important to me to
be involved in the church, um to be a
part of the body of Christ and to
interact with um believers and to
witness to the lost.
And establishing a family that's uh
that recognizes and seeks after the
things of God rather than the things of
the earth. And I believe that the people
that I've connected with over the years
and the ministries that I've been
involved with with
support group ministry. I've never been
to to seminary or Bible school in any
way. I've developed really deep
friendships and connections with people
in the body of Christ.
And when I became aware of what I had
heard was were changes in
um you know, just some of the popular
like videos and songs and some of the
pop culture things. I didn't really
think much about it. Uh but as soon as I
heard that someone said that they
thought scripture was changing,
I immediately perked up. Throughout my
30 years 30-plus years of walking with
the Lord, I felt impressed to really pay
attention to scripture that talks about
strong delusion and great deception. I
really felt in my spirit that we would
be living um in the last days. And
looking for scripture that really lays
out what those last days look like um
before the returning of our Lord.
It's it's imperative to understand what
that season looks like. I understood by
very definition is would be something
that we would not be able to define
before it happened.
Um and it's something that we should be
aware of and watching for. The workings
of the enemy in the end times is
something I've had my ear to the ground
to to just to be aware of what's going
on in the world and the seasons. And And
I I did not anticipate that God would
give me the eyes to see and the ears to
hear and to be what we are, which is
watchmen on the wall that have seen
something that is happening before the
body of Christ sees it. I've been going
one-on-one and speaking to as many
people that I can. I've spoken to dozens
about these changes. I feel compelled. I
feel very strongly that speaking to
pastors and speaking to church
leadership is imperative because
the body of Christ is starving. The body
of Christ is in darkness in so many
ways. There has to be a wake-up call.
And I pray that this is part of that,
that we're able to sound the alarm, to
share what we're seeing. We want to
share what God is showing us, what the
Holy Spirit is showing us because we are
seeing this crystal clear and we're
sharing with people and many of them
come back and just outright deny that
these changes are happening.
I believe this is the beginning of the
strong delusion uh that we talked about
in 2 Thessalonians, chapter 2.
Some changes that are clearly
blasphemous and some of them are
ridiculous.
But
my concern is
the church isn't awakened if they are
not aware that these things are
happening.
Because something is happening people,
you know, they're they're reading it and
they don't they don't see the changes.
They seem to remember it the way it is
now and most people will claim this is
the way it's always been.
But if the key prophecies
change,
my big fear is the Antichrist will be
able to use the Bible itself
and point to scripture
and make the claim that he is
our Lord and Savior returned. And to me,
that would be the culmination
of the strong delusion
where it says that they will believe the
lie.
And that would be the lie to believe
that the Antichrist is indeed our
savior.
So that is my biggest concern about
this. It's why I want to sound the alarm
and it's why we're doing this video is
we want those of you who are leaders,
pastors, elders, deacons,
if you see these changes, first of all,
even if you don't see the changes, this
is so important that you need you need
to study it cuz there's thousands of us
now that see the changes. I implore you
to take this to the Lord in prayer. Seek
the guidance of the Holy Spirit. Just
look into it.
Take a look at the things we're going to
be presenting, the scripture verses, and
let the Holy Spirit lead you because the
church needs to be awakened. They need
to understand what is happening before
it reaches the point that they just
simply won't have the ability to
distinguish what scripture was and what
it's become.
We've got thousands of people that are
seeing the same thing. Um I would have
never
thought that it would look anything like
this where um people would be seeing
changes in our physical Bibles. Yes, I
could see, you know, changes coming
through updates and through maybe video
form. Uh but we're talking about matter.
We're talking about physical things
changing. So
the delusion I think is really playing
off in particular a concept and a belief
that that the supernatural is really not
possible.
And I think that for all of us that see
we're we are definitely operating with
an understanding that the supernatural
is absolutely real. And
we are we've have the best evidence ever
that um you know, that there's
supernatural forces at work in our in
our lives now and we know it because the
scriptures have been hidden in our
heart. Because we have ingested the word
of God, because we have assimilated it,
because we have taken it to heart. And
when we compare what is in scripture now
versus what we have we know in our
heart, we are all seeing the same thing.
You know, we we all know and understand
that it was the lion that laid down with
the lamb, not
the wolf dwelling or now living. I think
there's been multiple changes on that.
Um with the lamb. So the strong delusion
is occurring and I believe the same way
as as Ernie is this is something that
now that we've become aware of it, we're
seeing it it getting stronger and
stronger. And yes, my big concern as
well is that the delusion will get
stronger and that people will have a
harder and harder time to see what's
happening. Um the longer it goes, it
seems like the harder it is to to get
people to see the changes. So, you know,
I would also add my
you know, sounding the alarm, imploring
that that seek the Lord while he may be
found. You know, seek the scriptures.
You know, look into this. Um pray so
that you will be able to know what's
happening um and be able to help those
around you that are that are seeing this
um
and you know, as a as a pastor to be
able to um help direct and to um put
this into context. Um and also for those
that are not seeing that they would be
warned.
So many of the changes scripture don't
even make sense. But before we go into
that,
I think it's important for us to be
very clear
on what we know is not happening.
And the reason why this subject is so
critical is because
there's a lot of new age
infusion happening right now with
this Mandela effect. We know that what's
happening right now is absolutely
satanic.
We know it's not God changing the Bible
because it's impossible for God to lie.
And we're seeing lies being embedded
into the Bible. Just stay with me for a
minute.
Please continue listening cuz we're
going to show you evidence of that.
We know
it is impossible for our creator to lie.
There is no unrighteousness
in him.
He is holy.
And we are seeing gross blasphemies
being embedded into the Bible right now.
This is not an issue of alternate
timelines or time travel
or adjustments made by God.
And it's very important that you hear
this
because there are some that call
themselves pastors
that are trying to debunk the Bible
changes.
And they're bringing up these parallel
universes. No, we don't believe in any
of that garbage.
We fully believe that Bible prophecy is
unfolding.
That it is appointed once for a man to
die and then comes judgment.
That's what the eternal truth
says.
It is appointed once, not multiple
times.
We do not live in parallel universes.
There is no time travel because if it
was an issue of time travel, we would
not be able to find residual on these
changes. And we find a plethora of
residual. And this has been documented
over and over again. It really is a
strong delusion.
And the enemy is messy. So we're finding
residual. Praise God.
And as as already been revealed this
evening is that there are thousands
of people across the earth that are
testifying of these changes
in their Bibles in every language and
every translation.
So please, we beg of you to search this
matter out and be courageous in this
hour.
You need to be willing to stand alone in
this. You need to be willing as a
pastor, church leader
to forsake everything and stand for
truth. Even if that means that you get
ostracized from your church, from your
denomination. It's not important. And
that's why we come before you and we're
passionate about this
that you as a Christian leader
would take a stand
for righteousness,
for truth.
With alternate timelines, I think
there's a really important concept to
really understand as believers. And that
is
in this fallen system, the you know, we
are living in the world, but we're not
of it. Um we understand that there are
all kinds of scientific facts or
theories that have been put forward.
Evolution being a huge one. Um now this
whole multiverse and alternate timelines
is is getting more and more popular.
Alternate timelines is the epitome of
hopelessness.
That every decision that a person makes
and that everybody makes
is happening at the same time or have
already happened. Idea that um all these
different decisions can lead all these
different timelines into the exact same
place in time and that it's possible
just to shift from one timeline to
another. Uh it's it's not a biblical
concept at all and it also breaks down.
I believe this is very much part of the
strong delusion where people are
believing an outright lie. That this is
not something that could even be
possibly true. Same thing with time
travel. Um you know, going back and
changing things um would have a
butterfly effect. So those
uh concepts I believe are rooted in
chaos, rooted in demonic and anti-God
perspective. There is one true word of
God, which is Jesus Christ.
The idea of time travel, if someone were
to go back in time and change what the
scribes wrote down,
that change would go forward in history.
Be no residual evidence to be found.
And that's one of the things that I
specialize on my channel is coming up
with residual evidence. And uh for those
of you listening that are pastors or
elders,
um I have found in the both the Hebrew
and Greek lexicons, um
several examples where
there's even quotes that are taken from
the King James Bible in these lexicons
that quote what was originally in the
scriptures.
So,
like I said, that type of evidence would
not be there if time travel were the
case. And as far as the timelines theory
goes,
if you subscribe or believe in the idea
that there are infinite number of
timelines,
then you would have to believe
that there Well, first of all, let me
say in scriptures that we will show you,
there are scriptures that talk about God
sending evil,
God sending evil spirits, God thinking
about doing evil.
So, if this timeline theory
were true,
that would mean that we would have
shifted into a timeline
where our God, our creator,
our king,
thinks about doing evil, sends evil
spirits, and brings evil. And that's
simply not true. All of us knew as
Christians that our God is holy, he's
just,
that he does not do any of those things.
So, that alone completely discounts the
entire timeline theory. So, what we're
dealing with is supernatural changes
that are happening within
our realm.
And like I said, those other two
theories just they don't stand up under
scrutiny. We have a series of of changes
we're going to be reviewing with you.
Again,
right now, brothers and sisters, you can
take out your King James Bible, but
every Bible and every translation is
changing, albeit differently.
But in the King James Bible, we're
seeing
on every page grammar errors and
spelling errors. The King James Bible
was a literary masterpiece.
It was
eloquent, beautiful.
Now we're seeing
a lot of nonsense verses.
And we're going to be covering these in
subsequent videos.
Get your King James
version of the Bible
and look through probably just five
pages, but let's let's just say 10
pages. Just read through 10 pages and
look for
where you have periods and question
marks followed by where the next word is
not capitalized.
And then also look and you will find
where there are commas and then the very
next word is capitalized.
How can it be a literary masterpiece
when it's just littered with these type
of grammar errors?
And and now to see these glaring
spelling mistakes, it's just it's
mind-blowing.
And then words that are not even
you know, a truly a word um
that are King James sounding
that it's just it's it's so crazy. I
mean, Deuteronomy 6:11 is filled with
three different just ghastly
spellings.
Um the word filledist, f i l l e d s t,
and then diggedist and plantedist.
It's mind-boggling that people aren't
seeing this as as being
a problem. That they can read this and
not catch it. It's like almost like a
child has tried to write King James
language.
We also see other grammar errors. Like
we see phrases like we be.
Or people is.
Or is become.
Or me thinketh.
Now friends, these are severe grammar
errors. This is not old English. What's
most important is that these changes are
obvious.
I also want to address other words that
we're seeing, like the word public that
has now a k at the end.
We're finding a lot of words that end in
c that now have a k at the end.
Like public,
garlic.
We also have music with a k.
Heretic with a k.
That's not how you spell those words.
We also have the word all wait in the
Bible.
And the changes go on
and on and on
with the spelling errors.
Those are some examples and we're going
to be showing more to you. So, brothers
and sisters, we've spent time
sharing with you grammar and spelling
errors that we're seeing in the King
James Bible.
In our subsequent videos, we will be
talking about more grammar and spelling
errors, name changes that we're seeing
in scripture, nonsense verses, doctrinal
errors,
and blasphemous
Bible changes. All the changes are
blasphemous and we're going to be doing
more research on these changes and
bringing them to the light. So, we want
to open up the dialogue with you.
We want to know what you think about
this. Do you see these changes?
Now with that said, we have a call to
action.
We are coming from a place of
uh depth um with God, understanding that
Bible prophecy is unfolding right now.
Our our call, our cry, our plea to you
is to first of all to recognize that a
lot of believers are seeing the same
thing right now. That has to speak
volumes. The supernatural is real. Also,
very clear admonition for us to watch
out for lying signs and wonders. And
there is a we have a very real
adversary. It's why what we're seeing is
so impossible for people to wrap their
minds around. There is a cognitive
dissonance, but we would implore you to
understand and see that the supernatural
is absolutely possible and it's
happening. We're operating as watchers
on the wall. That we are seeing these
things very clearly. And we are coming
together with a message to the
leadership of the church. We are praying
and seeking that there be a move of the
spirit that that people of God respond.
The Bible says that so many will will
lose
uh their focus and lose their way
because the hardening of their hearts
uh because of
uh their denying of the truth.
So, we implore you to seek truth and to
seek
and to seek God in this hour. Uh because
as we soften our hearts, as we yield our
hearts, as we repent,
as we seek the Lord on our face, as we
fast,
uh
we are
coming to a place of being able to to
see things clearly. And
we have a desire right now to warn the
bride of Christ. We have such a desire
for people to see what we're seeing. And
we implore you to spend the time to seek
the Lord in prayer, to research these
out yourself. Look at your own Bible
that you've studied from. See these
scriptures with spiritual eyes and you
will see what we see.
In the beginning was the word.
And the word was with God. And the word
was God. Jesus Christ is the word of
God. We are seeing
a perversion in our Bibles.
But the word of God endures forever.
No matter what they do to our Bibles,
it cannot change the word of God. You
probably thought the Bible could never
be changed.
Maybe you're still grappling with that.
I understand.
But I'm imploring you. I'm begging you
to wake up
and do your research.
Jesus Christ is the word of God. No
matter what happens to our Bibles, the
word of God
is eternal.
The wicked one is changing scripture.
He's changing times and laws. He's
bringing a famine in the land for
hearing the word of the Lord.
The word of God is eternal.
You need to understand that Jesus Christ
is not the Bible.
Do you understand that?
We don't worship the Bible.
We worship Jesus Christ in spirit and in
truth.
That is true. In the beginning was the
word, and the word was with God, and the
word was God. John 1:1. The Bible was
not in the beginning.
You do realize that, right? And that's
what we're talking about
right now. The word of God endures
forever, and the Bible itself is under
attack.
And there's a difference.
And that's what we're shining a light
on. And what we're reading in the Bible
is not the Jesus Christ
that we recognize. It is not the
scripture in the language that we've
hidden in our hearts. Jeremiah 29:11.
That's a favorite amongst many
Christians. It's a message of hope.
That's right. You remember that? It says
he will give us a future and a hope.
I remember that.
But now in the King James Bible
it says that we have an expected end.
Go look. Jeremiah 29:11.
But this is what we're talking about
with these Bible changes.
They're changing doctrine.
They're changing language. They're
changing the meaning.
And that's what we share with you today
as we continue.
Hi everyone. This is EYA, and it is the
second part of our series
directed towards pastors and Christian
leaders
about the Bible changes. We're seeing
throughout scripture, we're finding
grammar errors and spelling errors and
nonsense verses on every page.
And I beg of you, brothers and sisters,
to just open up your King James Bible.
And ask the Holy Spirit to open up your
eyes.
And we encourage you and implore you to
listen to the series in its entirety as
we show you what we are seeing in
scripture
that's changed.
In tonight's uh video
we're going to be sharing with you about
grammar errors, spelling errors, and
nonsense verses that are replete through
scripture from Genesis to Revelations.
Brothers and sisters, the King James
Bible was a literary masterpiece.
So in scripture, now we're seeing
changes to grammar and to spelling,
which anyone can see, whether you've had
contact with the Bible or not.
There are now words in the Bible that
aren't actually words.
And another way that that people are
looking at this is maybe this was just
King James language or
um, you know, an an older way of saying
things. But
there's so many examples that the the
wording has changed and the the actual
spellings have changed. Things like all
way
instead of always. The word sometimes
can be split. And words that we've
always known to be one word like today
or tomorrow or forever have now become
split in the King James versions. Words
that have always been multiple words
being combined into one.
So words that
are a stand-alone word that has multiple
words together like overplus.
Or this one especially, evil
favoredness.
A couple of words put together there,
but even the words don't make any sense.
So we're seeing these kinds of spelling
errors show up that
anyone should be able to see. We also
have words like resting place
and dwelling place that are normally two
words, but now they're one word.
We also have words like stumbling block
is now one word.
Those are just a few examples
of words that are either being separated
or they're being blended.
Then we have words that have no meaning.
Have no meaning that we've never even
heard of before. Like words like holpen.
That's right.
And then we have words like instead of
forget or forgot, we have
forgat.
Finding all types of crazy language
being embedded into scripture.
The word Judah is now spelled multiple
ways in the King James Bible.
Words like shamefacedness.
Men pleasers.
Stomacher.
We now see really crazy nonsensical
language being embedded into the Bible.
The nonsense continues. Thousands of new
words are being plopped into the Bible
that don't belong there.
We have pilots and passengers and planes
and rails and railing and slime and
gross and engines and college and
wardrobe
and network
and we have Mars and Jupiter and worlds
and planets
and gravity and space
and the list of words that are now being
embedded into the Bible are multiplying.
There are grammar errors and nonsense
verses on every page of the Bible and we
ask that you consult the Lord about
this. Ask the Lord to show you because
they're so obvious. And we're just going
to show you some examples right now.
Another thing that we're seeing are
capitalization errors in the King James
version of Bible. And these are they're
rampant. They're throughout the entire
Bible. Uh you can look on just about any
page and find them. Uh here are just a
few examples. For example, Joshua
chapter 7 verse 7 and it says in
Joshua said, "Alas, oh Lord God,
wherefore hast thou that all brought
this people over Jordan to deliver us
into the hand of Amorites to destroy
us?" And there's a question mark right
there after us and the next word is
would which should be capitalized, but
it's not.
Another example from the seventh chapter
of Joshua is verse 25.
And Joshua said, "Why hast thou troubled
us?" And again, we have a question mark
and the next word is thee, which should
be capitalized
and it's not.
And just to show that these
verses are in the New Testament as well
as the Old Testament uh we can take a
look at Mark
chapter 6 verse 3.
And this is something we see very
frequently with these grammar errors
that there are other problems with the
verses.
Who is Joses? I don't remember Jesus
having a brother named Joses, do you?
We have uh sentences that just don't
even make sense.
And we have verses like John 4 chapter 4
verse 7.
It says,
"There cometh a woman of Samaria to draw
water. Jesus said unto her, 'Give me to
drink.'"
Uh this isn't even proper English uh way
that you should ask someone for a drink.
So, we have all types of examples like
this where the sentence structure is
messed up, it doesn't make sense, and
there's all types of capitalization
errors that we see now.
In Zechariah 6:12
has several capitalization mistakes. Uh
definitely changed the branch is now
capital T H E. Um this the T is
capitalized. Branch is all capitalized.
Lord is is in here twice and all four
letters are capitalized.
Uh Lord is all four letters are
capitalized and H is not capitalized. It
should be Lord of hosts being the L and
the H capitalized.
Isaiah 9:6 now says today in the King
James Bible, "For unto us a child is
born, unto us a son is given, and the
government shall be upon his shoulder.
And his name shall be called Wonderful
Counselor
the Mighty God, the Everlasting Father
the Prince of Peace." And we see that
the titles and the names for God are no
longer capitalized.
This whole scripture verse is riddled
with grammar errors. And not only that,
but now we have the government resting
upon only one shoulder of Jesus.
The next In the next few minutes, we're
going to show you
images of scripture verses
that are nonsense.
So, these verses that we've talked about
looking at the the spelling changes, the
grammar errors, this is very difficult
for us.
We are used to the Bible being
perfect. The wording perfect, the
spelling perfect. Um knowing that we can
count on it for correct grammar, uh
knowing that we can teach from this
correctly, and knowing that it's
extremely clear. Now, that's not what
we're experiencing. And pastors,
leaders, we implore you to to notice
what we're noticing. Acknowledge or at
least come from a place of understanding
that there are so many people in the
body of Christ now that are seeing these
changes and are having real difficulty
assimilating this new information. To
know what it means and to be able to
navigate things in this hour. Uh we are
given clear evidence now that things are
changing in our physical world, that
there is a spiritual attack on the Bible
and we would implore you to acknowledge
and to study out these things for
yourself. Uh know that there are many
brothers and sisters in Christ in a
battle right now knowing and seeing
these changes when most are asleep and
not seeing these changes. So, we're
going to be looking at name changes in
the next video and it's so hard for us
to see these names just thrown into the
Bible now where we have not seen them
before. And you'll see exactly what we
mean as we get into this.
Thing that we want you to realize is
that breaking down the Bible and finding
mistakes and problems is not something
that we would have ever thought we would
be doing. It's painful for us to see so
many changes in the Bible. So many um
problems, so many uh grammar errors,
mistakes. And as we're going through
this, we're going to be getting into
even more serious problems that include
doctrinal errors.
Mount Zion
is known as Mount Sion, S I O N.
So as we're noticing all these changes,
our thoughts continue to go to what does
this look like a year down the road or
years down the road. People will not be
coming from a clear biblical view, they
will be coming through a corrupted view.
And we continue to see the words uh
continue to get worse. We continue to
see more blasphemous um changes, uh more
obvious changes that are
uh that are setting people up to see the
world differently.
One of the most shocking changes I found
was when I discovered that the word
Messiah had been fully erased from the
New Testament. In the King James Bible,
now it's only found twice in the Old
Testament in the book of Daniel.
Friends, and then we see something
shocking. The 12 tribes of Israel have
changed in the book of Revelations. In
verse 5, we have the tribe of Judah and
the Judah is misspelled.
We have the tribe of Asher when it was
Ashur, the tribe of the Nephthaleim,
that's right, instead of Naphtali,
like the returning of the giants. And
then we have the tribe of Manasses
instead of Manasseh.
And then in verse 8, we have the tribe
of Zabulon instead of Zebulun.
And also, we have a new tribe of Joseph
instead of Ephraim.
The 12 tribes of Israel have changed.
Here are the 12 tribes of Israel that I
remember,
certainly not as they're depicted now in
the book of Revelations.
Nebuchadnezzar
is now called Nebuchadrezzar sometimes.
We also see Hosea, the Old Testament
minor prophet, is now called Osee in the
book of Romans.
So now, Melchisedec
is now spelled
different ways in the Bible.
We see Timothy is now called Timotheus.
We also have John the Baptist is now
called John Baptist.
And then we see
Sarah of Sarah and Abraham
now being called Sariabram.
And then we have new characters in the
Bible like Aholibamah.
We also have Barak in the Bible.
And Cozbi.
And then we have in Romans 16 a whole
slew
of not just new characters in the Bible,
but new words in Romans 16.
Those of us who've been walking with the
Lord
for any period of time,
who have studied scripture, know that
Paul wrote the book of Romans.
And now we see something really shocking
in verse 22.
It now says I Tertius
who wrote this epistle.
Friends,
Tertius did not write the book of
Romans.
It was Paul. We're finding all types of
new characters with multi-syllables
that have been plopped into the Bible.
We also see many of the major
personalities from the Old Testament
are getting their names changed
in the King James version in the New
Testament.
For example, in Luke chapter 4, verses
16 through 21,
this is where Jesus takes the the scroll
of Isaiah
and he reads from the scroll and he
tells everyone,
"In your hearing of this, this prophecy
has been fulfilled."
But now, if you look in your Bibles, you
will see that Jesus is reading
from the book of Esaias.
I've never heard of Esaias before.
In Matthew 17, verses 1 through 4,
this is a the famous verse about the
transfiguration
where we see Moses and Elijah appearing
with Jesus.
But now, in the King James version, if
you read, what we see is Moses and
Elias.
Elias is a new name in the Bible.
Also, in Matthew 27,
verses 6 through 10,
where the chief priests pick up the
money that Judas received to betray
Jesus
and they used it to buy a field to bury
foreigners.
And in verse 9, the Bible tells us
that this fulfilled what was spoken of
by the prophet Jeremiah.
The only problem is is what we see now
in the King James version, it says the
prophet Jeremy.
So we're seeing
the names of major prophets
that were in the Old Testament, how
their names are being changed in the New
Testament.
Now, the King James translators, you
know, their charge, they were making a
translation for the common man
and they were trying to bring clarity
and simplicity. So, why would they
change the names of these prophets in
the New Testament? It only serves to
offer confusion.
This is not the way it used to be.
Isaiah's name was always Isaiah.
Elijah's name was always Elijah.
And Jeremiah's name was always Jeremiah.
Then we have the peculiar case of the
name of Noah in the New Testament.
In Hebrews 11:17,
1 Peter 3:20, and 2 Peter 2:5,
we still see in our King James version
today the name Noah.
However,
in Matthew 24, verses 37 and 38, we now
see Noe in place of Noah.
In Luke 3:36
and Luke 17, verses 26 and 27, we see
the same thing. We see the name Noe in
place of Noah.
Now, once again,
this makes absolutely no sense. Why
would the King James translators
translate this exact same Greek word as
Noe in some verses
and Noah in others?
It just serves for greater confusion.
I think all of us who have studied our
Bible and know our Bibles know that Noe
was never in
the New Testament.
As far as Matthew 24: 37 and 38,
I'm going to offer up my personal
testimony about this.
When I first started finding out about
these changes,
one of the things I was doing is trying
to find
proof or some type of evidence to
support the changes that we know are
there from our memories.
Now, this particular section of
scripture in Matthew 24 is a section of
scripture that I'm very familiar with.
And in late 2012,
I actually put together an outline for a
teaching.
And um
this uh Matthew chapter 24, these verses
37 and 38
were part of my outline. And what I had
done is I had taken directly off of
Bible Gateway
and I'd copied it, pasted it into my
outline.
So, when I found out that Noah's name
was being changed to Noe,
I remembered that I had done this this
outline, so I went back and on my
computer I found the outline
and I went to it.
And in that outline, in verses 37 and
38,
it still has Noah.
So, this is definitive proof for me that
it actually said Noah.
But furthermore, actually at that time,
verse 37 said Noe
and verse 38 said Noah.
Now, when I saw this,
I was thinking, this really makes no
sense and whoever's making these changes
is probably going to update this. So, I
thought that this might be a change. So,
what I did is I took my 1948 King James
Version
and I took a picture of these verses
where it said Noe and Noah.
And I had saved this picture and put it
on a flash drive thinking that, okay,
when this change takes place, if it
does, then I'll have some proof. Now,
also at this time, I had a friend of
mine
who I'd been telling about the Bible
changes and he told me, "I want to see
everything you've got, all of it."
So, I actually sat down with him
and this is one of the changes we went
over. I showed him the very Bible I'd
taken the picture out of. He looked in
it. He saw where it said Noe and Noah. I
showed him the picture I took.
So, now fast forward probably and also
at that time I told him that, you know,
I expected that this might change.
And of course, you know, he was kind of
new to the changes, you know, really in
shock about the whole thing, but he
really thought the idea that, you know,
this was going to change further was
really really out there and crazy.
Well, about 6 months later what happened
is it did change to Noe in both verses.
So, I immediately thought, great, I have
photographic evidence. I can prove to
people that this is a change.
So, I went and I got my flash drive and
I looked at the picture and to my utter
other shock and amazement,
it had changed to Noe in both places
in that scripture.
So, what I did is I got hold of my
friend
and I asked him, I said, "Do you
remember me showing this to you
in the Bible and about these pictures
and how I told you I thought this might
change?" He goes, "Yeah, of course I
do." I told him, "I said, get your Bible
and look at it."
And he was completely unaware
because he remembers what I told him.
So, I have my original residual evidence
in my outline where it said Noah.
And then I have my friend's testimony
who also witnessed where it was Noe and
Noah and then changed to Noe in both
verses.
So, for me personally,
uh this is
unequivocal proof to me. I know for a
fact
these particular verses changed because
I watched it happen over time.
Brothers and sisters,
pastors, elders, deacons, leaders of the
church, all we ask is that you examine
the evidence that we put before you.
We ask that you take this to the Lord in
prayer. Seek the leading of the Holy
Spirit as you listen to what we present
in these videos,
our personal testimonies.
We just pray and we ask that you take
this to the Lord in prayer
because the flock needs to be informed
of what's happening to their Bibles.
But I ask each of you
to look at your own Bibles. We're
talking about the King James Version,
but we're also talking about other
versions. These are very specific verses
that have to do with the way that we
perceive God, the way that we understand
his character, um the way that we
understand how God works. And it's also
touching on very key parts of
what we understand uh as far as
Christian worldview. Just want to make
sure that it's very clear how hard this
is for us to talk about. Again, we are
very much
aware that the Bible has been the
scriptures, the holy scriptures of God.
And we have had decades of walking with
the Lord and uh relying on scripture.
What we're seeing now is a perversion.
It is a change. It is a clear violation
of God's word. Uh it is a a darkness
that we're seeing. It is a uh a
different voice that's coming through
scripture. We implore you to seek this
out, to
to pray, to fast, to seek the Lord in
this hour. We all know that the Bible is
full of references to our coming Lord in
the Old Testament. Job 25:6
now refers to the Son of Man as a worm.
And in Luke 1:35,
it says that the Holy Ghost shall come
upon thee and the power of the highest
shall overshadow thee. Therefore also
that holy thing
which shall be born of thee shall be
called the Son of God.
Is this a blasphemous
title for the Son of God and calling him
a holy thing?
always seen scripture never
contradictory. What we're seeing now in
scripture are exactly opposite or
opposing positions in scripture. Uh we
have both Galatians 1:8 and then then 2
Corinthians 11:4 with completely
different perspectives in showing us how
we are supposed to respond to people um
that come to us and preach another
gospel.
So, in Galatians 1:8, we're being told,
"Let them be accursed."
But in 2 Corinthians 11:4, "Ye might
well bear with him."
So, on the one hand, he's supposed to be
accursed. On the other hand, we're
supposed to bear with him. We clearly
know that scripture has always indicated
that
any other gospel should be rejected.
Now, we're being told to bear with him.
We've all as believers, you know, heard
this parable many times and it's the
parable of the talents. Now, it's not
even the parable of the talent, the King
James is referring to pounds.
Specifically now, at the end of that
parable that we all know so well,
Jesus is talking, "But those enemies of
mine which would not that I shall reign
over them,
bring hither and slay them before me."
Not something that we recognize.
The other verse that I would like to
point out, story of Ishmael, where we
know that Abraham
had was married to Sarah and that Sarah
had a servant named Hagar.
Hagar, as we know, gave birth to an
illegitimate son that became the father
of the Arab nation and to Islam.
And now in scripture
look for yourself
Hagar has is the wife of Abraham.
So this legitimizes
the lineage of Ishmael.
Brothers and sisters, in this portion of
the video I'm simply going to share with
you
images
of Bible verses and passages
from the King James Bible
that have been obviously changed.
I ask that you pause the video
before we start looking at them and ask
the Holy Spirit
to give you wisdom and discernment and
understanding.
Earnestly desire truth.
We are warned that God would send the
strong delusion because they did not
love the truth and I need to ask you do
you love the truth?
Brothers and sisters these Bible changes
are so grievous to my spirit.
Is your spirit provoked within you?
Because if it isn't there's something
wrong
and you need to begin repenting. You
need to begin seeking the Lord because
these changes to scripture are so
obvious.
All throughout the Bible right now we're
seeing blasphemous Bible changes from
nonsense verses and grammar errors to
doctrinal errors.
It's unbelievable what we're seeing.
These are lying signs and wonders that
we were warned about bringing on the
strong delusion.
At this time let's look at the Hebrew
words Strong's number H7451.
As you can see in the King James version
translation count
this word has been translated many
different ways.
Most often as evil 442 times.
But hurt trouble
adverse
and harm are all legitimate ways to
translate this word.
Since the word can be translated in all
these different ways then it should be
clear
that the context of the verse in which
it appears is critical
how the word should be translated.
Keep this in mind as we look at some of
the verses where this word has been
translated as evil.
Here are just a few examples.
Joshua 23:15
Therefore it shall come to pass
that as all good things come upon you
which the Lord your God promised you
so shall the Lord bring upon you all
evil things
until he has destroyed you from off this
good land which the Lord your God has
given you.
Now in this verse we see
the Lord bringing evil upon Israel.
In Micah 1:12
for the inhabitant of Maroth waited
carefully for good but evil came down
from the Lord unto the gate of
Jerusalem.
In this verse we see evil coming down
from the Lord.
Now let's look at 2 Kings 21:12.
Therefore thus saith the Lord God of
Israel behold I am bringing such evil
upon Jerusalem and Judah
that whosoever heareth of it both of his
ears shall tingle.
Here again in this verse, we see the
Lord bringing evil.
1 Samuel 16:14-15.
But the spirit of the Lord departed from
Saul.
And an evil spirit from the Lord
troubled him.
And Saul's servants said unto him,
"Behold now, an evil spirit from God
troubleth thee."
In these verses, we see that an evil
spirit has come from the Lord.
Friends,
our God is holy.
He is righteous, and he is just.
He does not bring evil.
He does not send down evil.
And evil spirits do not come from the
Lord.
These verses provoke my spirit.
They should provoke your spirit as well.
Clearly, this Hebrew word should not be
translated as evil in these verses.
And I don't believe that the King James
translators made these grievous and
blasphemous errors.
These verses have been supernaturally
altered.
If you can't see that they have been
changed, I don't know what could
possibly convince you.
Let me show you two more verses.
Numbers 23:19.
God is not a man that he should lie.
Neither the son of a man that he should
repent.
Hath he said, and will it not be done?
Or hath he spoken,
and will he not make it good?
We learn from this verse that God does
not repent.
Because he's because he doesn't need to
repent.
Now, let me read this verse to you.
Exodus 32:14.
And the Lord repented of the evil which
he thought to do unto his people.
Now, in this verse, not only is the Lord
thinking of doing evil, but he is
repenting of these evil thoughts.
This verse is in direct contradiction to
what we read in Numbers 23:19.
There is no denying that this is a
direct contradiction in scripture.
And it depicts our Lord as thinking
about doing evil.
I can't think of a more blasphemous
attack on the Holy Scriptures than this.
As a pastor,
as an elder,
as anyone who has spent serious time in
the scriptures,
there is no way you can justify this
as having always been in our Bibles.
With changes like this occurring to our
scriptures,
how much longer can it be before Jesus
returns to put a stop to this kind of
blasphemy?
The bride of Christ needs to be awakened
and prepared to meet her king.
You are responsible for the flock.
You have been charged as an overseer to
protect them.
How will you answer?
Are you going to deny the changes?
Or are you going to warn the flock?
The scriptures have been very clear
about what the end times are going to
look like.
Uh we have all had in our hearts a
longing to be with our Lord. And we've
had an understanding because of Holy
Scriptures about the kinds of things
that will be uh going on and the things
that we will see
during those end days, the times before
the coming of our Lord.
So, I would point to second Timothy
3:2
that gives a description about the kinds
of behaviors that will be going on
uh in this time. Now, the King James
version has some errors in even in this.
But, we know that the people will be
blasphemous. They will be lovers of of
themselves instead of lovers of God. We
understand the kinds of behaviors that
will be happening in those end times
because scriptures have
have made that clear to us. It's in our
hearts, and we know what things will
look like because of the picture that
scriptures have painted of those times.
Brothers and sisters,
I ask you and to seek the Lord, to ask
yourself,
do we see the signs of the times now?
Are we looking at behaviors, mindsets,
uh
the the way that people interact with
each other?
Does this look like the the kinds of
behaviors that were foretold in
scripture?
I ask you to consider
the importance of us to be aware that
there is a great deception that we have
known to be coming.
We were That was foretold. It was
made clear to us to watch for that great
deception. Second
Thessalonians 2
is a an entire chapter that I encourage
you to to read, to to look into, to ask
the Lord about what is being shared in
the scripture. We are being admonished
and told that in the last days that
people will stop being lovers of truth.
And that they will not be seeking the
Lord.
So, I ask you,
if any of these scriptures that we have
been sharing to you
are apparent to you that they have been
changed, then consider that
what is happening now could fall under a
great deception, and it could be part of
a strong delusion.
We believe that the strong delusion is
now taking place.
We have laid out
scripture after scripture that we can
clearly see have been changed.
We are very aware that the scriptures
that are in our hearts are no longer
matching the Bible.
My question to you, and I ask you to
seek the Lord in this, is is it possible
that you are now seeing
the great deception? That you are now
seeing the strong delusion.
Is this
evident
to you by us showing you these things,
by laying out
scripture after scripture that we have
known to be true, that we have known to
be from from God, now being corrupt,
perverted, and demeaned?
The image that we were given of the time
that's coming is the lion laying down
with the lamb.
And we know now in scripture that the
wolf shall dwell with the lamb.
We implore you to consider that wolves
are now
operating in the body of Christ.
We beg of you
to start fasting and praying, to repent,
to ask the Lord to open up your eyes, to
take away the scales from your eyes so
you can see the truth in this hour
because there's not much time.
We're warning
the church. We're warning you, brothers
and sisters, out of love.
Out of love for the church.
Out of love for the truth.
Out of love for the purity of scripture
that's now been twisted and perverted.
We ask that you seriously take into
account everything we've shared with you
today.
Stop justifying the changes as if you've
been doing that.
And call upon the Lord
to give you eyes to see.
We beg of you. We implore you. We
beseech you
in love
in Jesus Christ.
For we desire that his children would
not be deceived in this hour. We were
warned over and over again, do not be
deceived.
Jesus Christ is living word of God.
He wants to be worshipped in spirit and
in truth. We do not worship the Bible.
The Bible is changing.
There is one God, only one,
and we bow our knees before him, the
King of kings and the Lord of lords.
We worship Jesus Christ in spirit and in
truth
because that's what he's called us to
do.
We ask that you come out and be separate
and let go of the things of the world
and pursue him.
Seek him. Cry out to him and we stand in
the gap and pray for you.
Yes, we do.
We pray that you will see
and you will understand the hour that
we're in
because the hour is so short. Wake up
out of your slumber.